

Ho Chi Minh City, VN

+84973877428

□ ducqhle@gmail.com

in linkedin.com/in/ducqhle

O ducqhle.github.io

## **Summary**

4 years of experience in software development. Has been responsible for and maintains high quality standards in every project involved. Contributed values to the project not only by getting the job done, but by constantly looking for ways to make it better. Keep a positive attitude towards every challenge with the mindset that technology is about getting better at solving problems. Looking forward to the opportunity to work abroad.

## Work experience

## **Full Stack Engineer**

2021-01 - present

Spiderbox Design

Closely and independently working with the co-worker's team from Australia to developing UX-UI for Energy products & services. Maintain codebase quality by participated in reviewing code including refactoring, adding Unit Tests to improve the coverage and increase maintainability for the product.

Proactively discuss the details and provide consultants to help increase user experience beside resolving issues and bugs to improve the product's reliability.

Tech stack: React, React-Bootstrap, Material-UI, NextJS, MobX, D3JS, Redux, MJML, PowerBI, VueJS.

### **Software Engineer**

2020-07 - 2021-01

Software Engineer

Participated in developing the core features for the chatbot-platform by involving in developing new feature while maintaining codebase quality. Researched solutions in order to implement chatbot application requirements and systems required specifications.

In addition, participated in configuring CI/CD process using Jenkins, Docker and integrate with Bitbucket, OpenShift. Participated in sharing knowledge and documenting technical specifications.

Technical stack: Botkit, Microsoft Bot Framework, Jest, MongoDB, Docker, Jenkins, Openshift, React, Node|S, TypeScript.

## Software Engineer

2018-09 - 2020-04

KMS Technology, Inc

Participated in grooming, sizing, and sending questions/solution reviews in order to clarify the project's requirements.

Participated in migrating a .NET legacy system from monolith to microservices by using AWS .NET core and NodeJS serverless services

Đức Lê -

Participated in developing team NLU integrated conversation chatbot assistant

Technical stack: ASP.NET Core, NodeJS, AWS Services, Docker, Microsoft Bot Framework, LUIS, QnA Maker.

#### **Engineer Intern**

2018-06 - 2018-09

KMS Technology, Inc

Research and applied Azure Cognitive Services and Microsoft Bot Framework to build FAQs chatbot application.

Technologies: Microsoft Bot Framework, LUIS, QnA Maker.

# **Education**

Bachelor's degree

2015-09 - 2018-06

University of Science

University of Science Bachelor's degree, Information Technology 2015 - 2018 Machine Learning and Web mining

# Certifications

- Udemy Certificate of Completion Learn and Understand NodeJS Udemy
- React The Complete Guide (incl Hooks, React Router, Redux) Udemy
- KMS Techcon Certificate of Appreciation KMS Technology, Inc.
- The Complete Guide to Advanced React Component Patterns Udemy
- Certificate of Completion Learn and Understand NodeJS